https://1percent.com/tos#privacy

Cart
0
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Compare
0
You have no items to compare.
Wish List
Looking for Wholesale?
Compare
Rolling Papers Vaporizers and Glass Water Pipes @ 1 Percent. The Original Online Headshop since 1995
Search:
Enter text to proceed
Search
Menu
Rolling Papers All Rolling PapersPre Rolled ConesRolling MachinesRolling AccessoriesRolling TraysStorage/ExtractionHerb Grinder/SiftersGlass Pipes SpoonsBats + ChillumsWaterpipes + RigsSherlocksHeady GlassNails, Slides + BangersPendantsAccessoriesGlass Pipe CleanersCombustion DugoutsHand PipesSpecial PipesGlass Pipes Glass SpoonsGlass BatsGlass Waterpipes + Dab RigsSherlocksGlass Slides, Nails and DomesGlass PendantsAccessoriesGlass CleanersDugout PipesHerb GrindersAccessories Metal Pipe PartsHookahsStash + StorageLighters and TorchesVaporizers Portable VaporizersDesktop VaporizersVaporizer PartsGrinder/SiftersStorageNewest Gear
Home
/
Terms of Service and Privacy
Legal Notices
Disclaimers
Copyright Notice
Trademark Statement
1 Percent Terms of Service
Reproduction Permissions
Newsgroup and Chat Services
Our Privacy Policy
Site Blocking Information for Parents
Disclaimer
All Pipes and smoking accessories sold at 1 Percent are intended for legal tobacco/smoking mixture use by adults (18 years or older) only. Any other use of such products, by minors or for use with controlled substances is prohibited by and may constitute a violation of International, Federal, State, and/or Local laws.
By entering the site, you: (1) signify your assent to 1 Percent Terms Of Service; (2) verify you are at least 18 years of age; (3) verify tobacco products, pipes, and smoking accessories are sold legally in your County/State/Country; (4) agree to use the products offered herein for legal and intended uses only; (5) verify you are not visiting with any malice towards 1 Percent; (6) by entering this site you are observing any and all local laws & (7) irrevocably waive any and all liability resulting from the purchase and/or use of such products. If you are under age 18 or do not agree, DO NOT USE OUR SERVICE.
U.S. SURGEON GENERAL’S WARNING: Smoking causes lung cancer, heart disease, emphysema, and may complicate pregnancy.
As smoking may be hazardous to one’s health, 1 Percent does not advocate smoking by any persons.
Copyright Notice
Copyright © 1 Percent Inc. All rights reserved. The material on this site is protected under the copyright laws of the United States and international conventions and is the property of 1 Percent Inc. The material on this site may not be reproduced and may not be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, distributed or otherwise used, except with the prior express written permission of 1 Percent, Inc.
Trademark Statement
1 Percent and One Percent are pending or registered trademarks of 1 Percent Inc.
1 Percent Terms of Service
PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF SERVICE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE. By using this site, you agree to abide by the terms and conditions below. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, do not use this site. We reserve the right, in our discretion, to change, modify, add, remove or otherwise amend all or portions of these terms and conditions at any time and without prior notice. Please check these terms periodically for changes.
1.	1 Percent CONTENT AND USER SUBMISSIONS
The contents of the 1 Percent site are intended for the personal, noncommercial use of its Users. All materials published on 1Percent.com (including, but not limited to news articles, photographs, images, illustrations, audio clips and video clips, also known as "The Content") are protected by copyright and other intellectual property laws, and are owned or controlled by 1 Percent, or the party credited as the provider of the content, software or other materials. User may not modify, adapt, translate, exhibit, publish, transmit, reproduce, create derivative works from, distribute, display, reverse engineer, decompile or dissemble, or in any way exploit, any of the Content, software, materials herein in whole or in part, and shall abide by all additional copyright or other notices, information or restrictions appearing in conjunction with any Content accessed through the Service.
User may download or copy the Content and other downloadable items displayed on this Service for personal, noncommercial use only, provided that User maintains all copyright and other notices contained in such Content. Copying or storing of any Content for other than personal, noncommercial use is expressly prohibited without the prior written permission from the Rights and Permissions Department, or the copyright holder identified in the individual Content's proprietary notices including copyright notice.
1 Percent is pleased to hear from Users and welcomes your comments concerning its products and Services. While we value your feedback, our company policy does not allow it to consider creative ideas, suggestions, or materials other than those it has specifically requested. We hope our Users will understand the intent of this policy is to avoid the possibility of future misunderstanding in the event projects or materials developed by 1 Percent staff seem similar to the creative ideas of any of our users. Accordingly, we ask that you do not submit to us any original creative materials or ideas.
In the event we request submissions from our Users, such submissions shall be deemed, and shall remain the property of 1 Percent. Such submissions shall not be subject to any obligation of confidence on the part of 1 Percent, and 1 Percent shall not be liable for any use or disclosure of same.
Without limitation of the foregoing, 1 Percent shall exclusively own all now known or hereafter existing rights to the submissions of any kind and shall be entitled to unrestricted use of the submissions for any purpose whatsoever, commercial or otherwise, without compensation to the provider of the submission(s).
FORUMS AND DISCUSSIONS
"Forum" means a chat area, bulletin board, or e-mail function offered by 1 Percent. User shall not upload to, or distribute or otherwise publish through, the Service any Content which is libelous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, profane, sexually explicit, abusive or otherwise violates any law. Please use your best judgment and be respectful of other individuals using the bulletin boards. Do not use vulgar, abusive or hateful language. Bulletin boards within these sites and services are provided to give our users an interesting and stimulating forum in which they may express their opinions and share their ideas. 1 Percent does not endorse the opinions placed on these bulletin boards. User acknowledges that any submissions (e.g. Letter to the Editor, Review or Commentary) may be edited, removed, modified, published, transmitted and displayed by 1 Percent. In addition, user warrants that all moral rights in any uploaded materials have been waived.
The Forums shall be used only in a noncommercial manner. User shall not, without the express approval of 1 Percent, distribute or otherwise publish any material containing any solicitation of funds, advertising or solicitation for goods or services, or to promote Web sites or online services which are competitive with 1 Percent.
While 1 Percent does not and cannot review every message posted by Users in the Forums and is not responsible for any content of these messages, 1 Percent reserves the right to delete, move or edit messages that it, in its sole discretion, deems are in violation of the law (including trademark and copyright law), or this Agreement, or are abusive, defamatory, obscene or otherwise unacceptable. Users shall remain solely responsible for the content of their messages.
ACCESS AND AVAILABILITY OF SERVICES AND LINKS
1 Percent contains links to other related World Wide Web Internet sites, resources and sponsors of 1 Percent. Selection of an ad banner or link redirects User off of 1 Percent to a third party. Transactions that occur between the User and the third party are strictly between the User and the third party and are not the responsibility of 1 Percent. Because 1 Percent is not responsible for the availability of these outside resources or their contents, User should direct any concerns regarding any external link to its site administrator or Webmaster.
REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES
User represents, warrants and covenants (a) that no materials of any kind submitted by User or 1 Percent's use thereof in accordance with the terms and conditions of this User Agreement, will (i) violate, plagiarize or infringe upon the rights of any third party, including copyright, trademark, privacy or publicity, moral rights, contract or other personal or proprietary rights; or (ii) contain libelous or otherwise unlawful material; (iii) constitute false or misleading indications of origin or statements of fact; (iv) slander, libel or defame any person or entity; (v) cause injury of any kind to any person or entity; or (vi) violate any applicable laws, rules, regulations or other governmental regulations; and (b) that user is at least 18 years old. User hereby indemnifies, defends and holds 1 Percent and all officers, directors, owners, agents, information providers, affiliates, licensors and licensees (collectively, the "Indemnified Parties") harmless from and
against any and all liability and costs incurred by the Indemnified Parties in connection with any claim arising out of any breach by User of the User Agreement or the foregoing representations, warranties and covenants, including, without limitation, reasonable attorneys' fees. User shall cooperate as fully as reasonably required in the defense of any claim. 1 Percent reserves the right, at its own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by User.
1 Percent neither represents nor endorses the accuracy or reliability of any advice, opinion, statement, or other information displayed, uploaded, or distributed through the Service by any User, information provider or any other person or entity IF 1 PERCENT, THE SERVICE, THE ACCESS SOFTWARE (DEFINED HEREIN) AND ANY MATERIALS PROVIDED IF 1 PERCENT OR THIRD PARTIES THROUGH IF 1 PERCENT AND THE SERVICE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS IF 1 PERCENT MAKES NO WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE OR PURPOSE, TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT OR ANY OTHER WARRANTY, CONDITION, GUARANTY, OR REPRESENTATION, WHETHER ORAL, IN WRITING OR IN ELECTRONIC FORM, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE ACCURACY OR USEFULNESS OF ANY MATERIALS PROVIDED THROUGH THE SERVICE. IF 1 PERCENT SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE TO THE USER OR ANY THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY DIRECT OR INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGE OR LOSS INCURRED IN CONNECTION
WITH USE OF THE SERVICE, THE ACCESS SOFTWARE OR ANY OF THE MATERIALS PROVIDED IF 1 PERCENT OR THIRD PARTIES THROUGH THE SERVICE, OR ANY DAMAGE OR LOSS INTERRUPTIONS, DELETIONS OF FILES, ERRORS, DEFECTS, DELAYS IN PERFORMANCE OF THE SERVICE OR THE ACCESS SOFTWARE, REGARDLESS OF THE CLAIM AS TO THE NATURE OF THE CAUSE OF ACTION, EVEN IF 1 PERCENT HAS ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE OR LOSS.
User hereby acknowledges that use of the Service is at User's sole risk.
SOFTWARE LICENSES
User shall have no rights to the proprietary software and related documentation, or any enhancements or modifications thereto, provided to User to access the Service ("Access Software"). User may not sublicense, assign or transfer any licenses granted by 1 Percent, and any attempt at such sublicense, assignment or transfer is void. User may copy such software for archival purposes only. User may not copy, distribute, modify, reverse, engineer or create derivative works from Access Software.
TERMINATION
1 Percent may, in its sole discretion, terminate or suspend User’s access to all or part of the Service for any reason, including, without limitation, breach of the Terms of Service.
Users of 1 Percent acknowledge that site administrators have the right to terminate use without notice for any User who restricts, inhibits or disrupts any 1 Percent event or attempts to alter or improperly access any feature or function of the site. A User's access may also be subject to termination if the User posts or transmits any illegal content; harasses or threatens any 1 Percent User or 1 Percent employee; posts content (including the creation of usernames) that is offensive or otherwise disruptive of 1 Percent activities; posts unsolicited advertising; or improperly impersonates a 1 Percent employee or other individual.
DISPUTES, CLAIMS, AND LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
User agrees to arbitrate all claims and disputes arising from the use of this site or any products or services provided by 1 Percent, in accordance with all applicable rules of the American Arbitration Association. (AAA).
User acknowledges that liability of 1 Percent, if any, for any and all claims or disputes arising from the use of this site or any products or services provided by 1 Percent shall not exceed the total sum of $100.00 U.S. Dollars.
This Terms of Service Agreement has been made in and shall be construed and enforced in accordance with New York law.
Please take time to review our entire site. You may send comments on the above terms of service, or any other matter relating to 1 Percent's presence on the Internet
Requesting Reproduction Permissions
No material contained on our Web site may be reproduced or redistributed without prior express written permission.
Newsgroup and Chat Services
1 Percent does not edit or pre-screen content that appears in newsgroups or chat areas, but the administrators reserve the right to remove content that they consider inappropriate. By accessing newsgroups or chat areas, you agree to be bound by the terms of service thereof. 1 Percent disclaims any liability with respect to content in the newsgroups or chat areas of 1 Percent .
Our Privacy Policy
1 Percent is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our products and Services. This policy may change from time to time so please review it periodically.
1.	HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION
1 Percent collects information in several ways. Some personal information is gathered when you register. During registration, 1 Percent asks for your name, e-mail address, and other personal information. Once you register you are given a 1 Percent Identification and are able to take full advantage of all our sites and Services.
1 Percent also collects personal information and financial information (credit card numbers) whenever members or visitors purchase products from us. Contact information is used solely to send orders, information about our company and promotional material from our partners to our customers in that order only. When necessary, contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer.
1 Percent does not disclose personal information it collects except when we have the User’s express permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith such disclosure is required by law.
To the extent demographic and profile data are collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitors' experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. Anonymous demographic information may be shared with advertisers and market researchers on an aggregate basis.
Wherever 1 Percent collects personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy.
COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING METHODS
A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. YOU ARE ENCOURAGED TO SET YOUR BROWSER TO DECLINE OUR COOKIES, HOWEVER Any area of our site which may be manipulated or asks you to "sign in" requires that you set your browser to accept cookies.
We use cookies in order to: (1) allow registered Users to access their accounts; (2) allow us to tailor our Web site to better match your needs and interests; and (3) allow us to better understand the how users use our site thus helping us focus our resources on features that are more popular with our users.
LINKS TO OTHER SITES
Our site does contain advertisements and links to other web-sites. By using these links to access these sites, the User understands a cookie may be assigned by such third party.
CONTROLLING ANG CHANGING YOUR INFORMATION
All Users of 1 Percent are encouraged to update their personal information and to be involved in our use of such information. Users may update their personal information, deactivate their membership or opt-out of receiving communications from 1 Percent by visiting here.
Opt-Out: Our site provides Users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.
Delete/Deactivate: This site gives Users the above option for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
SECURITY
We use industry-standard efforts to ensure the confidentiality of your personal information, such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers where appropriate.
PRIVACY OF CHILDREN
Our Web site is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our Web site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and do not permit registration by, and will not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13 years of age. This requirement is clearly posted during the activation process.
Site Blocking Information
The 1 Percent site was rated with ICRA (formerly the Internet Content Rating Association. Surely we've been blocked by many other adult filters as well over the last 24 years. In the event a minor is able to circumvent filtering software, we implement many additional checks to insure that no order is ever fulfilled to any person under the current legal age.
See Also:
1 Percent Customer Service
Sign Up & Get Deals
Events, New Products
Content + More. 0% Junk!
Same Day Delivery (NYC)
Delivery Schedule
About 1 Percent
25+ Years Online!
Made in NYC!
Sign Up & Get Deals, Events, New Products, Content + More. 0% Junk!
Same Day Delivery (NYC)
Delivery Schedule
About 1 Percent
25+ Years Online!
Made in NYC, Baby!
Copyright 1995-2020 1Percent.com. All Rights Reserved.
